Guide to the Benoni J. Truslow, Class of 1934, Sheffield Scientific School, Photograph Collection Documenting Life at Yale
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Benoni J. Truslow, Class of 1934, Sheffield Scientific School, photograph collection documenting life at Yale
1960-1975
RU 776
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
1
(3 boxes)
The collection consists of black and white photographs of Benoni J. Truslow (Yale 1934S) documenting Yale individuals, events, and activities, including reunions and graduation.
Truslow, Benoni J.
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 48-A (YRG 48-A), Yale pictorial records and collections.
Arrangement
Arragned by accession.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of black and white photographs of Benoni J. Truslow (Yale 1934S) documenting Yale individuals, events, and activities, including reunions and graduation.
Photographs; Truslow, Benoni J.; Yale University -- Pictorial works; Yale University -- Employees; Yale University -- Students; Yale University. Sheffield Scientific School. Class of 1934
- Photographs, Series I
  - Unidentified banquet scene, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Banjo players, 1973 January (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Stained glass window with hand of cards, 1971 January (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - "Some Propasals" by George D. Vaill [inspired by SDS], 1970 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Unidentified individuals, 1972, 1974, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Deckhoff, Melvin '53 with family and friends, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Rafferty, Walt and others, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - "Hennings-on-Saybrook", 1970 June (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Sleepy Hall and friend - 45thReunion, 1971 June (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Judge MacDonald Will Pronounce Sentence! - John L. Koehne '17 Yale Medal, 1966 February 19 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Ain't It a Wonderful World? - Two with Mustard!, 1970 October (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - "Le Mani dell'artista" - Professor Deane Keller, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - "Le Mani della stampatore" - George D. Vaill '36, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Le Mani del traduttore - Professor Thomas G. Bergin '25, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - I Collaboratori - Deane Keller, T.G. Bergin, G.D. Vaill at table with On Sepulchres by Ugo Foscolo, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Nathan Hale statue -back view through window, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Nathan Hale -second hanging, 1969 June 14 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Yalies, classes of 1773 and 1973 - 3 students with statue of Nathan Hale, 1969 September 30 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - "Nathan Hale, 1773 Welcomes Amy Solomon, 1973", 1969 October 6 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Residential colleges, 1970, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Wright Hall lion statue, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Dwight Hall, Connecticut Hall, Harkness Tower, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Dwight Hall and Linsley Hall, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Connecticut Hall - "Spring", 1965 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Morse and Stiles Residential Colleges, Payne Whitney Gymnasium, 1965, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Harkness Tower from Pierson, 1969 August (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Branford court and Wrexham Tower, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Payne Whitney Gymnasium, Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Divinity quadrangle, 1962, 1970, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Day Mission Library, Yale Divinity School -interior, 1972 April (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Peabody Museum, Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Kline Biology Tower, Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Ingalls Rink, Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Beinecke Plaza
    - Woolsey Hall, Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Commons Dining Hall, Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Beinecke Library, Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Aerial views of New Haven and the Yale campus, Undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - New Haven and campus street scenes, 1968, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Churches on the New Haven Green, 1965, 1970, undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Photographs, 1968-1973; Accession 2003-A-160
  - Individuals
    - Beach, Lou, 1971 January 21 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Becton, Henry P., '37S, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Blair, Edwin Foster, '24, 1969 June (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Brewster, Kingman, 1969-1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Bundy, McGeorge, '40, 1973 January (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Chapin, Melvin, '40, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Cutler, Melvin, '36, 1969 June (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Dwyer, Marty, '44, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Frank, Clint, '38, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Gambril, Howard, Jr. '29, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Grimes, Dave, '45W, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Holden, Reuben, 1968 October (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Pinney, Edward S., '17, 1972 June 18 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Robinson, Lu, '18, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Unidentified, 1968-1973 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Groups
    - Dekhoff, Melvin, '53 with family and friends, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Dempsey, Jim, '38 and Melissa Dempsey, '71, 1969 October 25 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - The Greenfields, '47, 1970 November (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Hincks, John L., '20 and family, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - The O'Hearns, 1969 November 22 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - The Howard Phelans, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Rafferty, Walt and others, 1969 October (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Swenson Ted, '67 and Ed Swenson, '40, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - The Swensons, '40, 1970 November (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - The Symingtons, '43, 1969 October 25 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Truslow, Ben, '34 and friend, 1969 October 25 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Walden, Tassie and Joe, 1971 February 5 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - The Bill Beineckes and Ogden Sutros, 1971 November 20 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - The Booth Hemingways and the Peter Ferraras, 1969 October 25 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Foy, Joe, '38 with Howie Coy, Jim Dempsey, Julie Demspey Coy, Larry Dunham, others [unidentified], 1969 November 22 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Morting, Del, '34 and C. M. O'Hearn, '24, 1971 November 20 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Gallard, Dick, '37 and Keri Keating, '73, 1973 October (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Harvie, Jim and Melissa Dempsey, 1970 November (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Deaver, Monte, 24S with Waldo Greene, '30, Ted Rudd, '24S, Ed Greene, '24S, 1972 November (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Unidentified, 1963, 1969-1973, undated (Box 2, Folder 8 - 9)
  - Courtyard through window, 1971 January (Box 2, Folder 10)